♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Okay. Are we rolling?
Yeah, but we’re upside down!
Hello, fellow students
of Kadic Junior High!
Your ace reporters
Milly and Tamiya are here
to bring you an exclusive
for today’s school news,
and it’s really big
since as I’m pretty sure
you already know
tonight is the big night.
The night of our
annual school prom.
Unfortunately, our cameras
weren’t authorized
to film the site where
the festivities will take place,
but I can make out
from where I’m speaking
the girl who might be crowned
our beauty queen tonight,
just as she was last year,
I’m mean, of course,
our principal’s daughter, Sissi.
Let’s see whether she’ll answer
a few questions.
Well, Sissi?
How about a few words
for our TV audience
before the big night?
Sorry, munchkins.
I only talk to real pro reporters.
I have no time to waste
on a couple of nerds!
But it’s for the school
news program!
What about freedom of the press!
Oh, Milly.
Little dipsticks your age
don’t have any freedom,
understand?
Anyway, who needs
your dumb reporting?
What do you know?
Besides, you’ve got a problem.
Don’t forget you have to have a date,
and I don’t know anyone
who’d want to go with a jerk like you.
Even them.
I’ll bet if you ask them,
they’d run like scared rabbits.
Who needs them!
There are lots of other boys!
Oh, yeah? What are you
waiting for, then?
Try and find one!
Uh, uh, Ulrich, would you…
would you be my date tonight?
Uh…I’m sorry, Milly.
It wouldn’t be a very good idea.
I’m too old for you.
And uh, well,
you see, I promised to go with Yumi.
You see?
What did I tell you?
But don’t worry, Milly.
I’m sure you’ll find a boy
for the sandbox dance.
Meanwhile, why don’t you
go play with your dolls?
Milly!
Milly, wait!
I hope you’re proud of yourself.
Aelita?
This is Jeremie.
Do you read me?
Aelita?
Hi! How are you?
I’m fine. How about you?
Okay.
I didn’t see anything unusual
around the towers.
It all seems quiet.
Well, for the moment.
You know, I’m making progress
with my research,
so…so you can
come and live with us.
The key to materialization?
You’ve found it at last!
Uh…well, no.
Not yet,
but I’m working on it.
It’s just a matter of time.
Then XANA won’t be able to
do anything to harm you or us.
That’s great! Thanks.
Milly, don’t cry.
We’ll go to the prom.
You’ll see.
As for the news,
Jim said it was okay.
We have until 9 o’clock.
Oh, it’s a waste of time.
Better face facts, Tamiya.
They don’t care about us
or the newscast.
Oh, I hate them.
All of them.
I hate every single
one of them.
I hate everybody
in the world.
You don’t know what you’re saying.
It’s just that--
Oh, stop it! I’m sick of you, too,
so just leave me alone!
Hey!
It’s true Ulrich could’ve been a little nicer.
Don’t look so gloomy, Ulrich.
Is it because of Milly?
You could’ve said yes.
You know, me and the prom.
Even if I was your date?
Sissi really did come on strong.
If meanness is one of the
qualities of a beauty queen,
she’ll get re-elected, alright.
That’s true, but try to get
Miss World to see that.
Ha-ha! Miss World, huh?
Miss In Her Own World
is more like it!
At least you don’t
care how old I am, do you?
We understand each other.
We’re not like those dumb older kids
who always want to run things.
They think that because we’re young,
we don’t count at all.
If for once we were older,
a lot older than them,
they wouldn’t laugh at us, would they?
Milly?
Are you in there?
Are you finished sulking?
Hurry, we have work to do!
Okay, okay. I’m coming!
You stay right there.
I’ll be back for you.
We have a report to finish
on the prom, remember?
(SINISTER MUSIC)
(GROWLING)
Hey, I hope you two aren’t gonna
follow me around all day long.
As far as I know,
you’re not beauticians,
so stop sticking to me like glue!
I don’t need you, understand? So scat!
Uh…Sissi…
w-we thought--
Take this advice.
Don’t think--
it doesn’t suit you!
-Oh.
A bunch of babies at our prom.
They’ve gotta be kidding.
And that other freak who had
the nerve to invite Ulrich!
Can’t believe it!
If anybody’s going out with Ulrich,
it absolutely has to be me.
I am the star--
the diva of the school!
(CREAKING)
Huh?
(PULSING)
Who’s there?
Answer me! Who is it!
(SCREAMS)
Move along. Back to your dorms.
Everything is just fine.
Looks as if we’ve
got ourselves a super scoop.
What do you say we take a look
to make sure that our old friend XANA
isn’t behind this?
Mhmm.
What do you think?
A simple short circuit.
Too many appliances
plugged in at the same time.
Yeah, the hi-fi, lights,
lady shaver, curling iron…
all together, what do you
expect to happen?
Not to mention
the brain stimulator!
Although she probably never
figured out how to use it.
Hmm.
I don’t know what happened,
but if you ask me, Sissi had it coming.
I couldn’tagree with you more.
Oh, no!
My teddy bear’s gone!
Aha!
Caught you!
It’s forbidden to play
in the garden shed!
Wait a minute, Jim!
It was my--
I don’t want to know why.
I’ve told you a hundred times that this place
is much too dangerous for children.
Look at all these rusty tools!
What do you think this is,
a kid’s playground?
We know, but--
No buts, huh!
Now, I hope I’ve
made myself real clear.
Entry forbidden.
Access reserved for adults.
With you, everything is off-limits!
Now, you listen here, huh.
I would change the way I talk
if I were you, little girl.
Little girl!
Okay, I’m young, so what!
It’s only big kids who can
say what they think, huh?
Ah, so you think
you’re real big kids?
Okay, that’s fine.
News report or not,
the two of you are grounded
for tonight in your room.
Oh great, Milly.
Really great.
Thanks to you,
it’s goodbye prom.
Now, beat it!
Oh, look at the pictures we’ve taked.
They’re really fantastic.
Something wrong, Milly?
Somebody stole our teddy bear.
And I’m sure it’s one of
the big kids who did it for spite.
Milly, you’re right! Look at this!
It’s a picture of Sissi’s room.
And there’s my teddy bear!
Hidden under her pillow! Incredible.
Ah, who would’ve believed it?
Soon, she’ll be playing with dolls!
Okay! Come on, now!
We gotta find her!
If Jim catches us in the dorm,
we’re in big trouble, Milly.
You go back to your room.
I’ll handle this.
(RUSTLING)
What’s going on now?
Who’s there?
Come on out!
D--aah!
Y-You’d better watch out!
I-I’m a black belt!
(GROWLING)
A-a-a-a-ah!
And now you’re sure, Jim,
that this is your attacker?
And you say he’s
an expert in martial arts?
I think it would be better
not to call the police. Right, Jim?
What happened to Sissi, it was…
it was kind of weird, don’t you think?
It was a short circuit.
A simple short circuit.
What else could it be?
I’m not so sure, and you know
just what I mean.
Anyway, let’s play it real cool.
Walls have ears, you know.
Well, I’ve got to go now
and get ready for the prom tonight.
Sometimes, being a day student
can be a total drag.
Don’t complain.
No one wakes you at 6 AM,
you have hot water,
and you don’t have to sleep
next to smelly Odd.
See you later.
Odd, are you looking for something?
Oh, uh, no.
You see, I just heard about
what happened to Jim.
Do they know who attacked him?
Uh, no.
For now, I think our gym teacher
could use some rest.
(GASPS)
XANA? In a teddy bear?
Yeah, I’m pretty sure.
He’s always there
when you least expect him.
Okay, guys.
Who goes and who stays here?
We can’t have a solo mission.
It’s too dangerous without Yumi.
If you go alone, you never know
what you’re gonna find over there.
I volunteer!
What did I just say, huh?
Well, have you got any other ideas?
There have been two accidents,
we can’t leave the school unguarded,
and even going back in time
if there’s an accident, it’s all over.
Odd is right.
You go and I’ll stay.
If I find any clues,
I’ll pass them on to you.
Go on and say hi
to you know who for me.
Aelita?
Aelita? Aelita, it’s Jeremie.
Do you read me?
Hi there.
We think that XANA
has launched an attack.
Have you noticed anything?
No, nothing.
But we can take a closer look.
Aelita, I’m sending Odd.
He’s coming over solo.
Ulrich has to say behind
to watch for any virus action at school.
Odd looks ready to go.
How are things with you, Ulrich?
It looks like we have a problem.
A big one.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner.
Virtualization.
Jeremie, it’s bad, huh.
The bear got out of the school.
If it’s under XANA’s control,
it’ll only become much madder.
It’ll go for anybody that’s around.
Especially his mortal enemies. Like you.
Huh!
Oh, Yumi!
You see that?
The tower that XANA has activated
can’t be too far away.
Well, uh, not down there, anyway.
Maybe on the neighboring plateaus.
Oops.
Too late.
Here come the reception committee.
Odd, take good care of Aelita.
(DIAL TONE)
Answer, will you! Answer!
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Odd, what’s going on?
Laser arrows!
Aaah!
Odd, you just lost
another 10 life points!
No kidding!
Odd, I’m afraid we haven’t any choice.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Ulrich! Watch it, will you?
Sorry. Are your parents home?
No, they went out.
Okay. Come on, we can’t stay here.
Hey, would you mind explaining?
Uh, we don’t have time.
Come on!
Odd, be careful.
You only have 50 life points left.
Laser arrows!
(SCREAMS)
We can’t leave you alone
for one second, huh?
Odd! I think I found something.
Oh, no!
That way!
(BOTH SCREAM)
Jeremie, it’s Ulrich.
Yumi’s with me.
We’re coming back to the school
to evacuate everyone.
Tell Odd to move it.
It’s getting rough around here.
Odd, hurry up.
Teddy’s getting real angry.
Okay, okay.
The tower can’t be too far away.
Let’s see now.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Houston, we’ve got a problem.
Odd still hasn’t found the activated tower.
You go and clear the dorms.
I’ll take care of the gym.
We found the tower, Jeremie.
Great, well done!
Now all you have to do is deactivate it.
Okay.
Just give me a minute to say hello
to an old buddy of mine.
Cut the courtesy!
You only have 50 life points left.
You can’t let him hit you!
Hey, Ulrich.
You could’ve made a little effort.
I don’t believe how sloppy you look!
Well, I’ll let it go this time.
Put it down to the company you keep.
Try to chill out and have fun.
You look like you’re expecting a disaster.
Ulrich! How are you?
Hey, where did your date go?
Next time, just call me.
And now the moment
you’ve all been waiting for!
The election of this year’s
beauty queen! So, get ready!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Gotta run now!
It’s my moment of triumph!
Now, that’s what I call
a really warm welcome.
Aaah! Aaah!
Jeremie, Odd’s not gonna
make it on his own!
Yes, he will!
Odd! Go on, you have to hit the target!
And now, everyone, this year, once again,
it’s time to elect the young lady
who in your view combines
more than any other girl,
charm, grace, beauty, and elegance!
And here is our first candidate!
Stop!
Listen to what I have to say.
You have all got to get out of here!
We have to evacuate the gym.
Now, keep calm…
I'm not joking. This is serious.
We are about to be attacked
by a gigantic teddy bear.
(LAUGHTER)
Ha! I knew it!
I saw it, too!
I saw the giant teddy bear, too!
Quiet, quiet!
Shut up, all of you!
You bunch of idiots!
Can’t you see what he’s trying to do?
It’s a trick, I tell you!
A trick to keep me from
winning again this year!
A gigantic teddy bear. Come on.
Why not King Kong while you’re at it?
(SCREAMING)
Odd, it’s now or never.
Aaah!
Impact!
Go on, Aelita. It’s up to you.
Ulrich!
Ulrich! Are you okay?
Yeah, sure.
Ready for a trip into the past, Yumi?
Ulrich, would you, uh…
would you…
would you be my date?
I’d be glad to, Milly.
I’ll see you here at eight.
Really?
Why, sure.
You’re not too mad at me,
are you, Yumi?
Not at all.
Anyway, my secret admirer
will take me tonight.
Right, Odd?
What!?
But, Ulrich, you’re gonna…
go with that…that silly baby?!
That’s right, I sure am.
But don’t worry.
When your brain gets
another neuron to two,
maybe I’ll go out with you, too.
You are recording, Tamiya, I hope.
You bet I am!
This is a scoop!
A super scoop!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO